Morrow Family papers, 1839-1966
Sophia Smith Collection
- Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow)
  - Morrow, Elizabeth (Cutter)
    - Correspondence with friends and associates (Box 43)
      - Chapman - Church of Christ (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Church Mission of Help - Colefax (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Colgan - Comstock (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Conant - Cosmopolitan Club (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Craighill - Cushman (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - Dake - Days (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Dean - d'Harnoncourt (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - de Selincourt - Dowdeswell (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Dowdeswell - Dwight School (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - E (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - F (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Gamiro - Graeme (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Grande Maison de Blanc - Hall (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Hallaran - Hildebrandt (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Hill - Hulst (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - Hulst - Ingalls (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - Ingham - Jordan (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Junior Assembly - Kassick (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - Kassick - Knickerbocker Club (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Kinsman, Rebecca, 1895-1915 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Knox County General Hospital - Lamont (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Lamont - Lewis, Elizabeth Dike (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Lewis, Laura - Lowthorpe School (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - MacArthur - McClung (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - McCook - Mexican Arts Corporation (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Mexican Arts Corporation - Miller (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Milton Academy - Morse (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Morton - Munroe (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Munroe - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - National Broadcasting Corporation - City of Northampton, Massachusetts (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - North Haven, Maine (Box 46, Folder 13-14)
      - Northover - Nuttal (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Oberlin College - Oviatt (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Pachard - Payson (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Peabody - Plimpton (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Poets' Guild - Reid (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Relief Society for the Aged - Rublee (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Rublee - Rutherford (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Sage - Schill (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Schladermundt - Sherborn, Ada (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Sherborn, Charles - Smith, Luther Ely (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - Smith, Mary - Stifer (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - Stimson - Theban (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - Thomas - Thornton (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - Thornton - Tyler (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - U - W (Box 48, Folder 2-4)
      - Wadmon - Walter, Alice Evangeline Hall (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Walter, Alice Evangeline (Box 48, Folder 6-8)
      - Walter, Alice Evangeline - Washburn (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - Washington and Jefferson College - Whitney (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - Whitney - Whitridge (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - X - Z, illegible names (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence soliciting or acknowledging donations, 1928-49 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence in French (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - Requests for autographs, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 15-16)
      - Miscellaneous third party, 1869-1940 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, incoming
      - Unknown to ECM, 1896-1936 (Box 48, Folder 18)
      - Unknown to ECM, 1937-54, undated (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
      - First name only, A-Z, 1930s-50s (Box 49, Folder 3-9)
      - First name only, 1893-94 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous, 1938 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Children's drawings, undated (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - Birthday and greeting cards
        - From miscellaneous or unknown, 1918-52, undated (Box 49, Folder 13)
        - Birthday cards from family, undated (Box 49, Folder 14-15)
        - Christmas cards: Morrow, Morgan, and Lindbergh families (Box 49, Folder 16)
        - Christmas cards, undated (Box 49, Folder 17)
        - Travel essay for Christmas by Corliss and Margaret Lamont, 1950 (Box 49, Folder 18)
        - Valentines from children and grandchildren, undated (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Organizations and activities (Box 50)
      - American Bankers' Association Convention: Women's Reception, 1922 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Christianity in Crisis, 1941-43 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Citizens' Committee for Planned Parenthood, 1938 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Colby College
        - Maine Million Fund, 1937-38 (Box 50, Folder 4)
        - Printed material, 1931-37 (Box 50, Folder 5-6)
      - Committee to Defend America by Aiding the Allies
        - Lend-Lease Bill Advocacy, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence with White, William A., 1940-41 (Box 50, Folder 8)
        - Printed material, 1940-41 (Box 50, Folder 9)
        - Clippings, 1940-41 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - Englewood (New Jersey) Community Chest
        [see also: Speeches]
        - Administration
          - Plan for the Campaign Committee, 1933 (Box 50, Folder 11)
          - Bylaws drafts, 1933 (Box 50, Folder 12)
          - Bylaws final copy and audit, 1933 (Box 50, Folder 13)
          - Membership lists, undated (Box 50, Folder 14)
          - Agendas and Minutes, 1933-34 (Box 50, Folder 15)
          - Reports, 1911-12 (Box 50, Folder 16-17)
          - Situation report and budget, 1933 (Box 50, Folder 18)
          - Englewood Survey, 1937 (Box 50, Folder 19)
        - Correspondence
          - Social Services Federation of Englewood, 1933-34 (Box 50, Folder 20)
          - 1932-53, undated (Box 50, Folder 21-22)
        - Printed material
          - How to Help, 1933 (Box 50, Folder 23)
          - SHARE! drafts, undated (Box 50, Folder 24)
        - Campaigns
          - Campaign Kit, 1933 (Box 50, Folder 25)
          - Chairman's manual, 1934 (Box 50, Folder 26)
          - Campaign materials, 1934-35 (Box 50, Folder 27)
        - Events, 1933-53 (Box 50, Folder 28)
        - ECM's notes for speech, circa 1933 (Box 50, Folder 29)
        - News clippings, 1933-34 (Box 50, Folder 30)
      - Fight for Freedom (Box 51)
        - Administration
          - Statement of purpose, agendas, finance, 1941-42 (Box 51, Folder 1)
          - Merger with Committee to Defend America, Oct-Dec 1941 (Box 51, Folder 2)
          - Membership lists, 1941 (Box 51, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence, Apr-Dec 1941 (Box 51, Folder 4)
        - Printed material: newsletters and radio speech, Sep-Dec 1941 (Box 51, Folder 5)
        - Affiliated Organizations
          - For Finland, Inc., Nov-Dec 1941 (Box 51, Folder 6)
          - Freedom House, 1941-42 (Box 51, Folder 7)
        - Continental Congress for Freedom, 1941 (Box 51, Folder 8)
        - Notebook, Nov 1941-Jan 1942 (Box 51, Folder 9)
        - News clippings, 1941 (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - Food for Freedom
        - Administrative
          - General, 1943-1946 (Box 51, Folder 11)
          - Statement of principles and purpose, 1943 (Box 51, Folder 12)
          - Board of Directors: minutes, 1943-36 (Box 51, Folder 13)
          - Executive Committee: minutes, 1943-46 (Box 51, Folder 14)
          - Other minutes, 1943 (Box 51, Folder 15)
          - Advisory Committee for children's publications on foreign relief (Box 51)
            - General, 1944 (Box 51, Folder 16)
            - "Too Young to Enlist" notebook contents, 1944 (Box 51, Folder 17)
          - Reports and proposals, 1943-47 (Box 51, Folder 18)
          - Financial materials, 1940-46 (Box 51, Folder 19)
          - Lists of contributors, undated (Box 51, Folder 20)
        - Correspondence
          - A-Z, 1943-46, undated (Box 51, Folder 21-24)
          - Weston, Harold, 1943-45 (Box 52, Folder 1-5)
        - Public Relations and printed material
          - Press releases and progress reports, 1944-46 (Box 52, Folder 6)
          - Bulletins, Jul-Aug 1945 (Box 52, Folder 7)
          - News releases, 18 Jan 1946-20 Jan 1947 (Box 52, Folder 8-9)
          - Articles, 1944-45 (Box 52, Folder 10)
          - United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration (UNRRA): pamphlet drafts, undated (Box 52, Folder 11)
          - Pamphlets, 1943, undated (Box 52, Folder 12-13)
          - Pamphlets, flyers, letterheads, 1943-46, undated (Box 52, Folder 14)
          - Food guides, undated (Box 52, Folder 15)
          - Form letters, May 1946 (Box 52, Folder 16)
        - Related organizations
          - Food and Agriculture Organization, 1945-46 (Box 52, Folder 17)
          - Girl Scouts, 1920-44 (Box 52, Folder 18)
          - "News from Belgium" bulletins, May-Sep 1944 (Box 52, Folder 19)
          - Union Label Feature Service press releases, 1944-45 (Box 52, Folder 20)
          - United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration, 1945-46 (Box 52, Folder 21)
          - Other press releases, 1943-47 (Box 52, Folder 22)
        - Events
          - Cleveland Conference
            - Speeches, Oct 1943 (Box 52, Folder 23)
            - Correspondence, A-Z, Aug-Oct 1943 (Box 52, Folder 24)
            - Program material, May-Oct 1943 (Box 52, Folder 25)
            - News clippings, 21-29 Oct 1943 (Box 52, Folder 26)
          - White House visit, Sep 1945 (Box 52, Folder 27)
          - Other events, 1944-46 (Box 53, Folder 1)
        - ECM's notes, 1946, undated (Box 53, Folder 2)
        - News clippings, 1943-46 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Foundation for the Emotionally Unstable Personality, 1951-52 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Little School, 1936-40 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Mobilization for Human Needs, 1934-37 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Museum of Modern Art, 1936-37 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Museums, 1939 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - North Haven Library, 1939-40 (Box 53, Folder 9-10)
      - Poetry Society
        - Poems, Feb 1924-Mar 1927, undated (Box 53, Folder 11-13)
        - Correspondence, 1925-41, undated (Box 53, Folder 14)
        - Newsletters, 1923-27 (Box 53, Folder 15-17)
        - Miscellaneous, 1923-27 (Box 53, Folder 18)
      - Prix Femina Americain
        - General, 1933-34, undated (Box 53, Folder 19)
        - Correspondence
          - Dauban, Jeanne, 1932-34, undated (Box 53, Folder 20-21)
          - A-Z, 1932-34 (Box 53, Folder 22-23)
      - Red Cross
        - Correspondence and clipping, 1917-18 (Box 53, Folder 24)
        - Confidential Memoranda on Armenia, 1919 (Box 53, Folder 25-26)
      - Shakespeare Club of Englewood, NJ, 1934-41 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Smith College
        [see also Biographical Materials]
        - General
          - Class of 1896 class list, 1936-40 (Box 54, Folder 2)
          - Book presented to ECM by students, 1940 (Box 54, Folder 3)
          - "Smith in Portrait" calendar, 1940 (Box 54, Folder 4)
          - Museum of Art: correspondence and catalog, 1932-45 (Box 54, Folder 5)
          - Address by Wilmarth S. Lewis on "The Trustee of the Privately Endowed University," 1952 (Box 54, Folder 6)
          - Printed material: Women in the field of science, 1948 (Box 54, Folder 7)
          - Seating chart, 1943 (Box 54, Folder 8)
          - Seven Sisters' World War II summer programs, 1941 (Box 54, Folder 9)
          - Artwork and photographs, undated (Box 54, Folder 10)
          - News clippings, 1916-54 (Box 54, Folder 11-17)
          - notes, undated (Box 54, Folder 18)
        - Class of 1896 Reunion Gift Committee: Sophia Smith homestead
          - General, A-Z, 1916-17 (Box 54, Folder 19-26)
          - Minutes and reports, 1916 (Box 55, Folder 1)
          - Correspondence, A-Z, 1916-17 (Box 55, Folder 2-8)
          - Ledger of pledges, 1916 (Box 55, Folder 9)
          - Wallpaper samples, circa 1916 (Box 55, Folder 10)
          - Pledge cards, 1916 (Box 55, Folder 11)
          - Receipts, 1916 (Box 55, Folder 12)
        - War Service Committee, 1918
          - Administration
            - General, 1918-20 (Box 55, Folder 13)
            - Reports
              - General, 1917-20 (Box 55, Folder 14)
              - Andrews, Hannah: Reports, 1918 (Box 55, Folder 15)
              - Memoranda and reports: London, Boston, Paris, 1917-18 (Box 55, Folder 16)
                [see also ECM: Bio: Travel: France, 1918-19]
            - Proposal for Boy Scout program in France, 1919 (Box 55, Folder 17)
            - Criteria and equipment for joining the Smith College Relief Unit (Box 55, Folder 18)
            - Miscellaneous: library booklist (Box 55, Folder 19)
          - Correspondence from Smith College Relief Unit
            - A, 1917-1919 (Box 55, Folder 20)
            - Andrews, Hannah D., 1917- Mar 1918 (Box 55, Folder 21)
            - Andrews, Hannah D., Jul 1918-1919 (Box 56, Folder 1-3)
            - B, 1918-19 (Box 56, Folder 4)
            - Biddlecome, Elizabeth, 1918-19 (Box 56, Folder 5)
            - Bliss, Elizabeth H., 1917-19 (Box 56, Folder 6)
            - Brown, Dorothy H., 1918-19 (Box 56, Folder 7)
            - C, 1917-19 (Box 56, Folder 8)
            - Chapin, Anne, 1917-25 (Box 56, Folder 9)
            - Clapp, Mary, 1919 (Box 56, Folder 10)
            - Clement, Fannie F., 1918-19 (Box 56, Folder 11)
            - D-E, 1917-18 (Box 56, Folder 12)
            - Emerson, Ellen, 1918-20 (Box 56, Folder 13-15)
            - F, 1918-19 (Box 56, Folder 16)
            - Fast, Louisa K., 1918-19 (Box 56, Folder 17)
            - Ford, Harriet Chalmers, 1917-27 (Box 56, Folder 18)
            - G-H (Box 56, Folder 19)
            - Gaines, Ruth
              - General, 1917-19 (Box 56, Folder 20-21)
              - Ladies of Grecourt contract, 1919-20 (Box 56, Folder 22)
            - Goddard, Jean T. J., 1918 (Box 56, Folder 23)
            - Greenough, Clara M., 1918-19 (Box 56, Folder 24)
            - H (Box 56, Folder 25)
            - Hooper, Catherine, 1917-18 (Box 56, Folder 26)
            - J-L (Box 56, Folder 27)
            - Lewis, Mary B., 1918-19 (Box 56, Folder 28-29)
            - M (Box 56, Folder 30)
            - Mather, Lucy, 1917-18 (Box 56, Folder 31)
            - Moore, Alice, 1919 (Box 56, Folder 32)
            - Parsons, Alice, 1918-19 (Box 56, Folder 33)
            - N-Q, 1917-19 (Box 56, Folder 34)
            - R (Box 56, Folder 35)
            - Read, Georgia W., 1918-19 (Box 56, Folder 36)
            - S, 1918-19 (Box 56, Folder 37)
            - Stevenson, Mary G., 1918-19 (Box 56, Folder 38)
            - T (Box 56, Folder 39)
            - Tallant, Alice Weld, 1917-18 (Box 56, Folder 40)
            - Thayer, Helen R., 1917-19 (Box 56, Folder 41)
            - Valentine, Frances, 1918-19 (Box 56, Folder 42)
            - W (Box 56, Folder 43)
            - Wilson, Martha, 1918 (Box 57, Folder 1)
            - Wolfs, Marie, 1917-29 (Box 57, Folder 2-3)
            - Young, Dorothy, 1918-19 (Box 57, Folder 4)
          - Other correspondence
            - Ladies of Grecourt publication dispute, 1920-22 (Box 57, Folder 5)
            - Regarding potential relief work, 1939-40 (Box 57, Folder 6)
            - Near East Unit, 1919 (Box 57, Folder 7)
            - ECM outgoing, 1918-20 (Box 57, Folder 8)
          - Printed materials
            - Women's organizations for war relief, 1917, undated (Box 57, Folder 9)
            - Application, appeal, articles, 1917-18, undated (Box 57, Folder 10)
            - News clippings, 1918-19 (Box 57, Folder 11)
          - Fiction by June Richardson Lucas and Elizabeth Biddlecome: typescripts (Box 57, Folder 12)
          - Affiliated Organization: Red Cross
            - Children's Bureau reports, 1917-18 (Box 57, Folder 13)
            - European War Work reports, 1917-18 (Box 57, Folder 14)
            - Hospitals in England (Box 57, Folder 15)
            - June Richardson Lucas: correspondence, 1917-18 (Box 57, Folder 16)
          - Photographs: Grecourt, Somme, undated (Box 57, Folder 17)
        - Four Million Dollar Fund
          - General, 1917-26, undated (Box 57, Folder 18)
          - Correspondence, 1919-22 (Box 57, Folder 19-20)
          - Notes, 1925, undated (Box 57, Folder 21)
          - Printed material
            - Campaign books, 1919-25 (Box 57, Folder 23-25)
            - Campaign books, 1919-25 (Box 58, Folder 1-5)
            - Promotional material and club events, 1919-25 (Box 58, Folder 6)
            - Script, "The Adventures of Ada Fund," by Constance McLaughlin, 1919 (Box 58, Folder 7)
            - News clippings, 1920 (Box 58, Folder 8)
        - Fiftieth Anniversary Gift
          - General, 1924-25 (Box 58, Folder 9)
          - Morrow family contributions, 1925 (Box 58, Folder 10-11)
          - Correspondence
            - Personal to ECM, 1925 (Box 58, Folder 12-19)
            - Pledges, A-F, 1925 (Box 58, Folder 20-23)
            - Pledges, G-Z, 1925 (Box 59, Folder 1-7)
          - Printed material: "Smith around the World," Jun 1925 (Box 59, Folder 8)
          - News clippings, Jun 1925 (Box 59, Folder 9)
        - William Allan Neilson Foundation
          - Minutes and notes, 1935 (Box 59, Folder 10)
          - Account statement, 1935 (Box 59, Folder 11)
          - Lists and figures, 1935 (Box 59, Folder 12-15)
          - Pledges, 1935-37 (Box 59, Folder 16-17)
          - Draft and circular letters (Box 59, Folder 18)
          - Correspondence
            - A-H (Box 59, Folder 19-26)
            - Hammond, May (Box 60, Folder 1)
            - Hartford National Bank and Trust Company (Box 60, Folder 2)
            - I-R (Box 60, Folder 3-5)
            - Snow, Florence (Box 60, Folder 6)
            - Stevenson, George: treasurer, 1934-35 (Box 60, Folder 7-8)
            - S-Z (Box 60, Folder 9-11)
            - Regarding Neilson's speech at AAUW, 1935 (Box 60, Folder 12)
            - Neilson estate, 1946 (Box 60, Folder 13)
          - Morrow family bequests (Box 60, Folder 14)
          - "What Next? or The Annual Report," play, 1935 (Box 60, Folder 15)
          - "Facts about President Neilson" and "Neilson's Successor" speech, 1937 (Box 60, Folder 16)
        - Seventy-Fifth Anniversary Fund
          - General: organization chart, 1946 (Box 60, Folder 17)
          - Committees
            - All-Smith Committee, 1947-50 (Box 60, Folder 18)
            - Campaign Committee, 1946 (Box 60, Folder 19)
            - Capital Gifts Committee, 1951-53 (Box 60, Folder 20)
            - Committee on Needs, 1945 (Box 60, Folder 21-22)
            - National Headquarters Committee: Minutes, 1946-Jun 1947 (Box 60, Folder 23-24)
            - Observance Committee, 1948-49 (Box 61, Folder 1)
            - Planning Committee: minutes, 1945 (Box 61, Folder 2)
            - Trustee Committee, 1947-48 (Box 61, Folder 3-4)
          - Financial material, 1937-50 (Box 61, Folder 5)
          - Correspondence and solicitations (Box 61, Folder 6-15)
            - Foundations and corporations, 1947-49 (Box 61, Folder 16)
            - Pledges, 1945-50 (Box 61, Folder 17-22)
            - Pledges, 1950 (Box 62, Folder 1)
            - Pledge correspondence (rejections), 1949 (Box 62, Folder 2)
            - Correspondence: contributions, 1949-50 (Box 62, Folder 3)
            - Letters of congratulation, 1950 (Box 62, Folder 4)
            - Letters of appeal, 1948-50 (Box 62, Folder 5)
            - ECM's public letters (Box 62, Folder 6)
            - ECM's "last call" letter, May 1947 (Box 62, Folder 7-8)
            - ECM's gift (Box 62, Folder 9)
            - Faculty salaries, 1948 (Box 62, Folder 10)
            - Inauguration and convocation, 1949 (Box 62, Folder 11)
            - Esther Lowenthal Chair: correspondence (Box 62, Folder 12)
            - Letters protesting honoring of Eleanor Roosevelt, 1950 (Box 62, Folder 13)
            - Snow, Florence, 1946 (Box 62, Folder 14)
          - Publicity (Box 62)
            - Message to all Smith fund workers, report on Publicity activities: draft (Box 62, Folder 15)
            - News Bulletins, 1946-47 (Box 62, Folder 16)
            - News releases (Box 62, Folder 17)
            - News clippings, 1947 (Box 62, Folder 18)
            - Student fundraising, 1946 (Box 62, Folder 19)
          - Publications and speeches
            - "To New Usefulness and Honor": draft, 1946 (Box 62, Folder 20)
            - "Tax Aspects of Giving": correspondence and drafts, 1949-50 (Box 62, Folder 21-22)
            - Speech by Guy Emerson, 1947 (Box 62, Folder 23)
          - Events and fundraisers
            - General (Box 62, Folder 24)
            - Convocation and Inauguration of President Wright, Oct 1949 (Box 62, Folder 25)
            - Mexican Market, 1947-50 (Box 62, Folder 26)
          - Notes and lists, 1945-50 (Box 62, Folder 27)
          - Notes and lists, 1945-50 (Box 63, Folder 1-4)
        - Ginling College
          - Administration
            - Alumnae Committee for Ginling College (of the Alumnae Association of Smith College), 1920-41 (Box 63, Folder 5-6)
            - Twenty-fifth Anniversary Committee
              - Membership lists, 1940-41 (Box 63, Folder 7)
              - Committee minutes, 1940-41 (Box 63, Folder 8)
              - Meetings: Philadelphia, Pittsburgh, Worcester, 1940-41 (Box 63, Folder 9)
              - Clippings, 1940-41 (Box 63, Folder 10)
              - Events, 1940-41 (Box 63, Folder 11)
              - Lists of guests and patrons, 1940 (Box 63, Folder 12)
              - Silver sale for 25th anniversary fund, 1941 (Box 63, Folder 13)
              - Financial reports and memoranda, 1940-41 (Box 63, Folder 14)
              - Twenty-fifth Anniversary financial report
                - Smith Alumnae, 1941 (Box 63, Folder 15)
                - General, 1941 (Box 63, Folder 16)
              - Fundraising letters, 1938-41 (Box 63, Folder 17)
              - Fundraising notebook, 1940-41 (Box 63, Folder 18)
              - Publicity, 1940-41 (Box 63, Folder 19)
              - Programs and speaking engagements, 1940-41 (Box 64, Folder 1)
              - Donations and notes, 1936-41 (Box 64, Folder 2)
              - Correspondence A-Z, 1931-41 (Box 64, Folder 3-10)
            - General correspondence, 1936-42 (Box 64, Folder 11-13)
          - Printed material
            - The Pioneer, 1919 (Box 64, Folder 14)
            - Bulletin of Ginling College, 1919 (Box 64, Folder 15)
            - Printed materials
              - 1936-41 (Box 64, Folder 16)
              - 1940-43 (Box 65, Folder 1)
            - Reports and news bulletins, 1936-42 (Box 65, Folder 2)
            - Plays and Pageants, 1935, undated (Box 65, Folder 3)
          - Artwork: central building, undated (Box 65, Folder 4)
          - Photographs, 1935-41, undated (Box 65, Folder 5)
        - Committee on Furnishing the New Dormitories (Box 65, Folder 6)
          [see also Oversize]
          - Costs, 1925-26 (Box 65, Folder 7-8)
          - Correspondence, A-Z, 1925-26 (Box 65, Folder 9-13)
          - Notebook, 1926 (Box 65, Folder 14-15)
          - Morrow House bookplates and Bliss Carman poem, 1925-26 (Box 65, Folder 16)
          - Morrow House list of books given to library, 1925-26 (Box 65, Folder 17)
        - Institute for the Coordination of Women's Interests
          - General, 1925-27 (Box 65, Folder 18-19)
          - Articles by Ethel Puffer Howes, 1925-29 (Box 65, Folder 20)
        - Smith Clubs
          - New York
            - General
              - 1929-33 (Box 65, Folder 21)
              - 1935-46 (Box 66, Folder 1)
            - Opera benefit, 1913-36 (Box 66, Folder 2)
          - Chicago, 1936-49 (Box 66, Folder 3)
          - Miscellaneous, 1935-38 (Box 66, Folder 4)
        - Alumnae Association
          - Correspondence
            - General, 1918-52 (Box 66, Folder 5-10)
            - Florence Snow, 1938-43 (Box 66, Folder 11)
          - Semicentennial Committee: minutes, 1931 (Box 66, Folder 12)
        - Alumnae House Fund
          - General, 1930-37 (Box 66, Folder 13)
          - Building proposals and plans, 1931-32 (Box 66, Folder 14)
          - Architects' reports, 1932 (Box 66, Folder 15)
          - Building Committee